everybody pretty excited to be here
大家都很高兴来到这里
my name is Eduardo Solis fab your car
我的名字叫爱德华多·索利斯（Eduardo Solis）
value Cavallo you can make a joke saying
值卡瓦洛你可以开个玩笑
it from Mexican goes into a bar and
来自墨西哥的东西进入酒吧
finds a Brazilian
找到一个巴西人
we work for PayPal as the title of the
我们以PayPal为标题
presentation I'll give you a hint
演讲我会给你一个提示
and we're actually based on beautiful
而我们实际上是基于美丽
Sony really hard Austin Texas the
索尼真的很难得克萨斯州的奥斯汀
purpose of our presentation is to take
我们演讲的目的是
that you with us through our fantastic
你和我们一起通过我们的梦幻
journey of modernizing Java development
Java开发现代化的旅程
at PayPal it has been a long journey to
在PayPal，要经历一段漫长的旅程
get to where we are right now and
到达我们现在所在的位置，
especially in light of this conference
特别是根据这次会议
we want to show you what we have done
我们想告诉你我们做了什么
for micro services and specific how we
针对微服务，以及具体如何
have adopted spring boot in the last
最后采用弹簧靴
release of our framework so we work for
发布我们的框架，以便我们为
a group in PayPal call I think it's
贝宝通话中的一个小组，我认为是
called a cloud platform and
称为云平台，
infrastructure were basically part of
基础设施基本上是
the framework team our team has been
我们团队的框架团队
responsible for bringing Java to the to
负责将Java引入
the new era we have one of the most
新时代，我们拥有最
successful internal frameworks of all
所有人的成功内部框架
times in in in Java I just to give you
我用Java来介绍一下
an idea here's a couple numbers and this
一个想法，这里是几个数字，这
is this is not Java as a whole in in
这不是整个Java
PayPal this is just our sliver like this
贝宝这只是我们的条子
is the modern the new platform so
是现代的新平台，所以
there's about a little over 300
大约有300多一点
applications are now in production
应用程序现已投入生产
taking traffic or processing payments of
收取流量或处理以下款项
those 247 our services and when I say
那些247我们的服务，当我说
services this basically means restful
服务，这基本上意味着宁静
services external and internal there's a
外部和内部服务有一个
policy in PayPal that that a service
贝宝（PayPal）中的政策，即该服务
puts an API out and it can be used
放出一个API即可使用
outside or inside and and they had to go
外面还是里面，他们不得不走
to a very tight API spec there's about
到非常严格的API规范
50 batch applications that process tons
50批处理吨的应用程序
and tons of tons of jobs and there's
和大量的工作机会，还有
about 32 what we called message D
大约32我们称之为消息D
monster actually really services but
怪物实际上确实在服务，但是
instead of exposing restful api is there
而不是暴露宁静的api
just exposing messages the
只是暴露消息
they just consume messages from from
他们只是消耗来自
different services we have our own
我们拥有自己的不同服务
infrastructure basically these
这些基础设施基本上
applications today and actually I had a
今天的应用程序，实际上我有一个
different number yesterday but the new
昨天的号码不同，但是新的
number came came late last night this
号码是昨晚来的
this little stack is taking 5.1 billion
这个小小的栈花了51亿
calls per day there's a number of hits
每天有很多点击
how do we know what that our framework
我们如何知道我们的框架
is heavily instrumented there's a lot of
仪器齐全，有很多
metrics you can get out of it including
您可以使用的指标包括
the number of developers that are
的开发人员数量
working on it so we have about 1100 give
正在努力，所以我们有大约1100个
or take engineers that are given point
或选择有经验的工程师
in time working on these on this
及时处理这些
framework which brings to the support if
支持的框架
you if we the more proprietary the more
您，如果我们越专有，就越
obscure API is that we put in this
晦涩的API是我们放入了
framework the more difficult we'll make
框架，我们将变得更加困难
it to use works against us because we
使用它对我们不利，因为我们
have about 1,100 guys that can come with
大约有1100个人
a question and say hey how do i how do I
一个问题并说嘿我该怎么办
solve it we've noticed that by sticking
解决它，我们注意到坚持
to things like spring and open source
像春天和开源之类的东西
projects we can say let me google that
我们可以说的项目让我用谷歌搜索
for you we send them the link and they
为您，我们给他们发送链接，他们
find their solution so quickly make
如此迅速找到解决方案
thank you from how we're going to give
谢谢你我们将如何给予
the presentation we wanted to do some
我们想做的介绍
live coding but then we decided that hey
现场编码，但后来我们决定嘿
we're gonna stick this to PowerPoint and
我们将其粘贴到PowerPoint上
develop person without coding but for
培养没有编码的人
this for this one we're just going to go
为此，我们将要去
with PowerPoint I'm gonna give you an
使用PowerPoint我会给你一个
history of the architecture and PayPal
架构和PayPal的历史
there's been a lot of talks about the
有很多关于
monolith or how to break it into micro
整体式或如何将其分解成微型
services I was actually pleasantly
服务我实际上很愉快
surprised in this conference to see how
在这次会议上感到惊讶，看看
far we have come in PayPal into going to
到目前为止，我们已经进入Pay​​Pal，
the micro services journey he started a
他开始了微服务之旅
while back so I'll give you a quick
一会儿回来，我会尽快给你
overview for that just to give context
概述只是为了提供上下文
about what are the current developer
关于当前的开发者是什么
needs a PayPal
需要一个贝宝
people is are now a polyglot stack but
人们现在是多语言的堆栈，但是
what is one of the challenges for the
挑战之一是
the the the overall community and
整个社区和
specially the Java guys I was introduced
特别是介绍我的Java专家
to our framework it has a internal it's
对我们的框架来说，它有一个内部
known as raptor for the fighter jet not
被称为战斗机的猛禽
for the dinosaur
恐龙
how we came to be how we brought it
我们如何成为我们带来它的方式
in-house and then we're going to talk
内部，然后我们要谈谈
about our latest router release and
关于我们最新的路由器版本以及
father is going to give an overview of
父亲将概述
how we search it to use a spring boot as
我们如何搜索它以使用弹簧靴作为
supposed to be an in container Tomcat
应该是容器中的Tomcat
based framework and all the other
基于框架和所有其他
learnings from that all the of the
从中学到的所有东西
problems we had to face and how we solve
我们必须面对的问题以及我们如何解决
them we're going to quickly conclude
他们，我们将很快得出结论
with where we're gonna take this
带着我们要去的地方
framework from here now that we're in
从这里开始，我们现在在
spring food and we're actually looking
春天的食物，我们实际上正在寻找
at this brand new ecosystem of spring
在春天这个崭新的生态系统中
cloud and console and some of these
云和控制台，其中一些
other exciting exciting technologies
其他令人兴奋的令人兴奋的技术
coming on and then we're gonna leave
来，然后我们要离开
some time for Q&amp;A so let's quickly take
进行问答的时间，让我们快速进行
a look at a PayPal so okay PayPal was
看看PayPal，好吗，PayPal是
born in 1999 at the time there was
出生于1999年
nothing about C++ and CGI no emergency
没有关于C ++和CGI的紧急信息
or so up to 2004 PayPal was a monolith
直到2004年，PayPal还是一块巨石
there were a couple of applications
有几个应用程序
around this monolith but basically was
围绕这个整体，但基本上是
this big huge C++ application running
这个巨大的C ++应用程序正在运行
CGI all written in C++
CGI全部用C ++编写
there was the there's a story that
那里有个故事
somebody printed that source code and
有人打印了该源代码，
they put it out in outside of one of the
他们把它放在一个
largest of our tallest buildings in
我们最高的最高建筑物
PayPal and it was actually like going
贝宝，实际上就像去
back and forth to x was a lot of paper
到x的来回纸很多
in the probably killed a lot of trees
在可能杀死很多树木的地方
that they and of course he was not
他们，当然他不是
allowing the business to move at the
允许企业在
speed that it that it needed so 2007
速度，因此它需要2007
arrives the monolith is mostly
到达整体
unsustainable and then there's these new
不可持续的，然后有这些新
there are two to two things happen
有两到两件事发生
there's there's something called as the
有一种叫做
somebody created something called the
有人创造了一种叫做
Atlas framework which is basically géza
Atlas框架基本上就是géza
so ax approach to development in paper
所以斧头纸上的发展方法
except that they didn't want to use soap
除了他们不想用肥皂
they evaluated soap they didn't like it
他们评估了肥皂，他们不喜欢
they decided to use and I think at the
他们决定使用，我认为
time was attracted to use a binary
被吸引使用二进制的时间
protocol but what kind of following soap
协议，但是什么样的肥皂
semantics with posts and RPC style
帖子和RPC样式的语义
but it was all C++ at the same time
但这是同时所有的C ++
another project starts okay let's break
另一个项目开始好吧，让我们休息
this model it into services let's let's
将此模型建模到服务中，让我们
break it into pieces now that we have
现在把它分解成碎片
the Atlas framework and so we began our
Atlas框架，因此我们开始了
journey into distributed computing if
进入分布式计算
you want to call it that brought a lot
你想称它带来了很多
of new challenges that we've talked
我们谈到的新挑战
about in this conference right
关于这次会议的权利
distributed tracing how do we how do we
分布式跟踪我们如何
know and trace how a call goes from
知道并跟踪呼叫的去向
point A to point B to Point C to point D
A点到B点C点到D点
to yet again
再次
what is the latency how can I measure
我如何测量延迟
that how can I have visibility to all of
那我怎么能看到所有
this into the system so way back then we
进入系统，然后回到我们
started that journey 2008 it just
开始了2008年的旅程
coincided that the first two frameworks
碰巧前两个框架
for Java were introduced there was a lot
Java的介绍很多
of resistance in the beginning to
在开始的抵抗
adopting Java because the at the time
采用Java是因为当时
the mantra was well C++ is fast it's so
口号很好，C ++很快
fast that Java is really not going to
Java真的不会这么做的快
cut it is just not just low so there was
削减它不仅是低，所以有
a lot of challenges going in and
面临许多挑战，
bringing java to the stacks and for that
将Java带到堆栈中
reason it actually was brought by two
它实际上是由两个人带来的原因
different groups of people there were
那里有不同的人群
there was a group that was trying to
有一群人试图
bring it to the front end and saying hey
把它带到前端并说嘿
web applications and and then the Java
Web应用程序，然后是Java
is the choice now in the industry
是当今行业的选择
outside let's try let's try to do that
外面让我们尝试让我们尝试做到这一点
and they started with a fresh spring MVC
他们从新鲜的春季MVC开始
built on top of something that we
建立在我们所拥有的东西之上
inherited for me they call UK box
对我来说，他们称之为英国盒
environment which was eBay in a box it
盒子里是eBay的环境
was a kind of very legacy but very
是一种非常古老但又非常
old-style
老式
Java programming model so it had that
Java编程模型
going for them spring MVC was a
去他们春天MVC是一个
first-class citizen but at the time was
头等公民，但当时是
all XML it was a it started to grow and
所有XML都开始增长，
it became a kind of a heavy framework
它变成了一个沉重的框架
with a lot of proprietary components to
有很多专有组件
it at the same time in parallel there's
同时并行有
a there's a service stack D was actually
实际上有一个服务栈D
built to support that that proprietary
支持该专有技术
protocol from from the Atlas framework
来自Atlas框架的协议
we called it a SF and it kind of looked
我们称它为SF，看起来像
like axis
像轴
under the on the top but it was really
在顶部，但实际上
kind of weird because he was doing this
有点奇怪，因为他正在这样做
this proprietary protocol and that one
这个专有协议和那个
didn't have spring in the beginning a
一开始没有春天
spring was added later but it was more
春天是后来添加的，但更多
like a second tour of okay yeah we'll
就像第二次巡回演出一样，我们会
bring it so far so they keep paper
到目前为止，他们保持纸张
growing they allow developers to start
成长，他们允许开发人员开始
adopting Java people makes it as a
采用Java人使其成为
mainstream language in Java it's Orion
Java的主流语言是Orion
paper which was great but in 2014 there
纸张很棒，但2014年在那里
was a decision to say hey it doesn't
决定说嘿
make sense that developers have to learn
开发人员必须学习才有意义
two frameworks they don't share a core
他们没有共享核心的两个框架
or they kind of sort of share the core
或者他们有点分享核心
but you basically couldn't move from one
但你基本上不能离开一个
to another seamlessly you had to learn
无缝地学习
one and then had to learn the other
一个然后必须学习另一个
there were a lot of proprietary api's to
有很多专有的api
it and a lot of proprietary tricks that
它和许多专有技巧
you had to go and look at documentation
你必须去看文档
inside PayPal like if you if you googled
在贝宝（PayPal）内部，就像您是否通过Google搜索
it you would get no hits because look
它不会因为点击而获得成功
they don't they don't do the stuff that
他们不，他们不做那些
the paper knows so there was a an idea
本文知道所以有一个主意
to to create a unified stack with a with
用来创建一个统一的堆栈
a more modern approach to Java at the
一种更现代的Java方法
same time PayPal and eBay were merging
同时PayPal和eBay合并
technologies
技术
the idea was hey why do we have a Bey
这个想法是嘿，为什么我们有一个拜
labs and paper labs why don't we just
实验室和纸质实验室为什么我们不只是
have everybody combined into this one
大家都合并到这个
big unit and and we just produce
大单位，我们只生产
technology for both so this was a great
两者的技术，这真是太好了
opportunity for us to take the core that
是我们抓住核心的机会
eBay had created and that was already
eBay已经创建了，那已经
called Raptor and we put a lot of would
叫做Raptor，我们投入了很多
we change a couple of things in there to
我们将其中的几项更改为
adapt to a more modern Java stack and
适应更现代的Java堆栈并
this is today we're now talking
今天是今天我们在谈论
microservices we have a path is
微服务我们有一条路是
proprietary we are doctor icing our
专有，我们正在为我们锦上添花
environment we can we can build docker
我们可以构建docker的环境
containers with applications we actually
具有我们实际应用的容器
have the notion of remote config for a
具有远程配置的概念
while the the for those of you that have
而对于那些拥有
been going to the spring cloud workshops
一直去春季云研讨会
and you can see how you can do this
您会看到如何做到这一点
remote config and the application pulls
远程配置和应用程序拉
it I will have had that for a while it's
我将有一段时间了
pretty sophisticated
相当复杂
were we're trying to adopt a more robust
我们是否正在尝试采用更强大的功能
we have service discovery but it's very
我们有服务发现功能，但是
rudimentary we're gonna try to go we
基本的，我们要去
with a more sophisticated solution we
通过更复杂的解决方案，我们
have been talking about resiliency
一直在谈论弹性
patterns we had adopted hystrix for a
我们采用hystrix的模式
while now ourselves so this is where we
现在我们自己，所以这是我们的地方
are let me talk a little bit about the
让我谈谈
developer challenges of paypal you're
贝宝对开发人员的挑战
going to see it's probably the same
会发现可能是一样的
challenges that you have in your in your
内在的挑战
companies it's not unique PayPal
公司不是唯一的PayPal
developer has to be very agile the
开发人员必须非常敏捷
payment space is very competitive right
支付空间非常有竞争力
now there's fierce competition with a
现在有一个激烈的竞争
lot of companies PayPal is trying to
PayPal正在尝试的许多公司
innovate in a lot of different fields so
在很多不同领域进行创新
they need applications to be cranked out
他们需要启动应用程序
really quickly those applications need
那些应用程序需要的很快
backing services there's there's a lot
支持服务有很多
of the business is very aggressive from
的业务从
wanting results really fast at the same
想要非常快的结果
time you have this type very tight tight
你这种类型的时间很紧
deadlines to deliver this these new
交付这些新产品的截止日期
applications these new capabilities but
应用这些新功能，但
I have to have high quality because you
我必须有高质量，因为你
don't want first impressions to be bad
不想第一印象不好
there's there's there's a lot of issues
这里有很多问题
that happen when PayPal gets into
当贝宝进入
trouble it's a lot of money that you
麻烦你很多钱
lose so there's a lot we have very
输了，所以我们有很多
sophisticated continuous delivery
复杂的连续交付
automated testing tooling around being
围绕存在的自动化测试工具
able to to figure out if we have boats
能够弄清楚我们是否有船
or not we're a payments company security
还是我们是支付公司的证券
is number-one concern for us we're one
对我们来说是第一位的关注点
of the few companies that since the
自
beginning have done SSL all the way all
一开始都已经完成SSL
the way to the sir to the to the back
先生到后面的方式
end most companies tend to terminate as
大多数公司倾向于终止
a cell in the front we go all the way
我们前面的一个单元格
but that's just one that's just one
但这只是一而已
aspect right we have to deal with a lot
正确的方面，我们必须处理很多事情
of security authentication authorization
安全认证授权
policies a whole lot of things on top of
在很多事情上制定政策
that we have compliance we have to be
我们必须遵守
compliant with PCI DSS a lot of the
符合PCI DSS的很多
paper a lot of the payment space
纸很多的支付空间
requirements and it's very it's very bad
要求，这非常非常糟糕
if we get out of this we will we can go
如果我们摆脱了这一点，我们将可以去
out of business
停业
so it's very very strict to have log
因此拥有日志非常非常严格
scrubbers we have a lot of things that
洗涤器，我们有很多东西
prevent PII data from being exposed and
防止暴露PII数据，以及
you know these are these are things that
你知道这些是这些东西
our developers have to to deal on a day
我们的开发人员必须每天处理
to day basis maintainability of
每天的可维护性
applications but at scale patching an
应用程序，但大规模修补
application or putting a new release a
应用程序或发布新版本
new service that has new capabilities at
具有以下新功能的新服务
the scale that we talked about some of
我们谈到的规模
the hard core some of the really core
真正的核心
services they have pools of about 500
他们拥有约500个服务池
boxes so there's gonna be a strategy the
盒子，所以会有一个策略
past has to be able to patch that I'm
过去必须能够修补我
not patchy in a single swipe but have
一次刷卡时不斑驳，但有
smarts right like I'm gonna roll 10% I'm
聪明，就像我要掷10％我
on a monitor okay that's good let me go
在监视器上，好吧，让我走
to the next 20% and the developer is not
到接下来的20％，而开发商则没有
gonna be clicking a button you know can
将要单击一个您知道可以的按钮
you imagine 500 boxes and you're
你想象有500盒，
clicking the bottom 500 times so you
点击底部的500次
gotta have these very sophisticated
要有这些非常复杂的
tooling we've gotta ensure that every
工具，我们必须确保每个
new release or every patch that you put
新版本或您放置的每个补丁
out there that you keep
你在那里保持
backwards-compatible api's there's
向后兼容的api有
there's a lot of API standardization in
有很多API标准化
paypal is very this very strict very
贝宝非常非常严格
stringent how we do versioning how we
我们如何严格执行版本控制
roll traffic it's it's a fairly complex
吸引流量这是相当复杂的
business and you cannot break backwards
业务，你不能倒退
compatibility because I need to reduce
兼容性，因为我需要减少
failure into the rest of the system one
故障进入系统其余部分
of the problems with with micro services
微服务的问题
and distributed computing every
和分布式计算
application has to have great
应用程序必须很棒
performance we don't want to have 5,000
我们不想拥有5,000的性能
boxes where we can actually do the job
我们可以实际完成工作的盒子
with 200 that's pretty expensive we got
有200个，我们很昂贵
to be able to scale we've got to be able
为了能够扩展，我们必须能够
to flex up flex down and we got to know
屈曲屈曲，我们知道
about resiliency patterns what happens
关于弹性模式会发生什么
if the downstream services or what do i
如果下游服务或我该怎么办
do do i go to another service to tell
我可以去另一家服务店吗
hey stand this transaction and then
嘿，站在这笔交易，然后
recover it later there's there's a lot
稍后恢复它有很多
of things that can be done and even in
可以做到的事情，甚至在
the payment space when when services go
服务何时付款空间
back finally the business the business
最后回到生意
really wants to have visibility into
真的想了解
these new applications that come in how
这些新应用程序
many people are hitting them who are
很多人打他们
they
他们
is this product attracted to this sector
该产品是否吸引了该领域
of the population
人口
how much money is this making well they
他们赚多少钱
have some key performance indicators
有一些关键的绩效指标
that they're tracking all the time so
他们一直在跟踪
your application has to be instrumented
您的应用程序必须经过检测
with the ability to create these
具有创造这些的能力
dashboards to give you all of these
仪表板为您提供所有这些
business insight into what's going on
商业洞察力正在发生的事情
finally operations they need to know how
最终他们需要知道如何操作
many transactions per second are you
每秒有很多交易
taking per node or pool PayPal as a
将每个节点或池PayPal作为一个
whole and we're seeing deviations
整体，我们看到了偏差
injuria so late so is your performance
这么晚受伤，你的表现也是如此
degrading with your performance ok how's
表现不佳好吗
your memory how's you how's your CPU
你的记忆你怎么样你的CPU怎么样
utilization all of that stuff and the
利用所有这些东西和
frame again developers have have to
再次框架开发人员必须
provide this so it's a lot of stuff we
提供这个，所以我们有很多东西
don't want every developer having to
不想每个开发人员都必须
worry about all of this so by the way
担心所有这些，顺便说一下
there's no room for error here
这里没有错误的余地
you can't remember what the study is but
你不记得研究是什么，
I think every second is like in the
我想每一秒钟就像
order of $60,000 that get lost or more I
损失了60,000美元或更多的订单
don't know what the exact number is but
不知道确切的数字是多少
we cannot go down we cannot lose
我们不能下去我们不能失去
transactions we have a very aggressive
交易我们非常激进
99 like things like four nines so a
99喜欢四个九
couple couple couple seconds every here
这里每隔几秒钟
and there our our our availability one
还有我们的可用性
is the goal it affects our bonuses so
是影响我们奖金的目标
that's one paper we believe in
那是我们相信的一篇论文
frameworks they provide built-in support
他们提供内置支持的框架
for a lot of these concerns you don't
对于很多这些问题，您不会
have to worry about security the way
不得不担心安全性的方式
PayPal needs to do it you need to worry
贝宝需要这样做，您需要担心
about certificate management key
关于证书管理密钥
management they give this foundation so
管理他们给这个基础
that the developers can actually focus
开发人员实际上可以集中精力
on writing the products and writing the
在撰写产品并撰写
business our frameworks are highly
商业我们的框架是高度
instrumented we have been doing
我们一直在做的
distributed tracing we got sip King
分布式跟踪，我们喝了一口金
actually that shows us exactly for a
实际上，这恰好向我们展示了
given transaction that like if you can
给定的交易，如果可以
go and say hey I remember that one year
去说嘿，我记得那一年
ago I had this transaction I had this
以前我有这个交易，我有这个
correlation ID you can go to that system
您可以转到该系统的相关ID
and you can still see how how is how the
而且您仍然可以看到如何
flow in the system was
系统中的流量为
you can see what the latency was on
您可以看到延迟时间
every hop inside the services developers
服务开发人员的每一步
don't have to do anything they just have
不必做他们仅有的任何事情
to write their business logic we do it
写他们的业务逻辑，我们做到了
for them another thing that we noticed
对他们来说，我们注意到的另一件事
with frameworks is they give common
与框架是他们给共同点
patterns for developers to use so for
供开发人员使用的模式
example let's talk about spring based
我们来谈谈基于弹簧的例子
framework if you know spring you can
框架，如果你知道春天，你可以
code in our frameworks you can move
您可以移动我们框架中的代码
inside PayPal if you're wondering the
在PayPal内部，如果您想知道
risk team you can actually go to the
风险小组，您实际上可以去
payments team and you're basically using
付款团队，您基本上是在使用
the exact same constructs you're
与您完全一样的构造
familiar with with the technology that
熟悉的技术
you're using it's not like a map my
你正在使用它不像是地图我的
plays with what you have to learn
玩弄你必须学习的东西
relearn everything every time an overall
每次都重新学习所有内容
frameworks make life easier
框架使生活更轻松
most of the time so what is Raptor
大多数时候，猛禽是什么
Raptor is our modern Java framework
Raptor是我们现代的Java框架
stack again in 2014 we set up about
2014年我们再次成立
building it there was there was a raptor
那里有一个猛禽
already in the ebay side it shares a
已经在eBay端共享了一个
common code with our paypal raptor but
与我们的贝宝猛禽共同的代码，但
we decided to slide in modern design
我们决定采用现代设计
principles when we got it we knew it had
我们知道的原理
to be cloud ready pass ready and it
准备好云准备通过
should have it allows a DevOps model
应该具有允许DevOps模型的功能
developers can actually deploy their own
开发人员实际上可以部署自己的
their own applications they decide when
他们自己的应用程序，他们决定何时
they push code they control their pools
他们推送代码，控制池
operations is there or all the way
操作在那里或一直
they're monitoring things together
他们正在一起监视事物
everybody there's a lot of cell service
每个人都有很多细胞服务
a lot of operation and development
很多运作与发展
coexistence
共存
so what design principles we started and
那么我们开始的设计原则是
this is this is kind of crucial of how
这是如何
we ended up in spring boot first of all
我们首先以春季靴结束
we did two of the problems that the
我们做了两个问题，
sorry one of the problems big problems
对不起问题之一大问题
are the other two frameworks the
是其他两个框架
previous frame was had was that they
以前的帧是他们
used this they ended up using a lot of
用这个，他们最终使用了很多
proprietary technologies and again that
专有技术
brings the problem of support having to
带来必须解决的支持问题
learn things that the industry you bring
学习您带给行业的东西
somebody from from from the from the
某人从
outside they had they had this huge
在外面，他们有这么大
learning curve for these frameworks
这些框架的学习曲线
so we decided hey want to be as much
所以我们决定嘿想成为
standards-based as we can and by
我们尽可能地并基于标准
standards-based sure J SRS and all of
基于标准的肯定J SRS和所有
that but also the fact of standards
那也是标准的事实
things like spring these are a couple of
春天之类的东西
the ones that we that we picked some of
我们挑选了一些
the technologies one of the big
最大的技术之一
commitments that we have is we keep this
我们拥有的承诺就是保持这一承诺
up to date now we try to go to the
到目前为止，我们尝试去
latest release of a lot of our open
我们很多开放的最新版本
source products that we use in-house of
我们内部使用的原始产品
course we have to have some common
当然我们必须有一些共同点
components some proprietary components
组件一些专有组件
that are paper specific do we have
有纸质的吗
certain technologies in the back end
后端的某些技术
that they're not industry standard and
他们不是行业标准，
we have to adapt with them the previous
我们必须适应他们以前的
frameworks had a lot of static singleton
框架有很多静态单例
factories like get singleton get sold
像获得单身人士的工厂被出售
instance methods we decided to go with a
我们决定使用的实例方法
more modern approach of a component
组件的更现代方法
inside we were inspired by the OSGi way
内部，我们受到了OSGi方式的启发
of doing things that gel also very well
做的事情也很好地凝结
with dependency injection from spring
从春天依赖注入
and one said ok for every component that
一个对每个组成部分都说好的
we're gonna do this is the rule every
我们要做到这是每一个规则
component has to expose its
组件必须公开其
functionality through an API the API is
通过API实现的功能
packaged separately from implementation
与实现分开包装
consumers of the component only know
组件的使用者仅知道
about the API that allows us to switch
关于允许我们切换的API
implementations to wrap them up at
打包它们的实现
different paces as long as we adhere to
只要我们坚持不同的步伐
that API and it has proven to be very
该API，它已经被证明是非常
very clean a very clean way to to
非常干净的一种非常干净的方式
deliver our components even between
即使在
components they don't know about each
他们不了解的组件
other they only know about their API and
其他他们只知道自己的API，
Spring has been a fabulous the spring
春天是美妙的春天
core has been a fabulous framer to be
核心一直是一个神话般的策划者
able to wire all those things together
能够将所有这些东西连接在一起
as we embarked into into into this
当我们开始进入这个
journey we started becoming a really
旅程，我们开始成为一个真正的
good at spring on one of our tendencies
在我们的一种倾向下擅长春季
we're not going to have factories
我们不会有工厂
anymore we're not we're gonna move a
现在我们不是，我们要移动
little bit from the away from the the
一点点远离
design patterns from the from the group
来自该组的设计模式
of four not famous book instead we're
四本不出名的书
gonna do everything through dependency
要通过依赖来做一切
injection the production of
注塑生产
functionality is relies on the
功能取决于
dependency injection gods so for example
依赖注入之神，例如
here we're injecting a web target for
在这里，我们为
those of you that might not be familiar
你们那些可能不熟悉的人
web target is a standard API client for
Web目标是用于以下方面的标准API客户端
jax-rs this is this is the standard API
jax-rs这是标准API
to consume Webster restful services
消耗Webster宁静的服务
provided by jax-rs for those of you that
jax-rs为您提供的那些
had dealt with this you know that under
已经处理了这个，你知道
the covers you have to create a client
您必须创建客户的封面
it's a very heavy object you have to
这是一个非常重的物体
keep it around from the client you pass
与您通过的客户保持距离
a route and you get the web target so
一条路线，您就可以找到网络目标
you say build target and then you can
你说建立目标，然后你就可以
you pass the base URL and then you get
您传递基本URL，然后得到
it out so we wanted to extract all of
出来，所以我们想提取所有
that from our consumers why do they have
来自我们消费者的原因
to keep track of the clients we can keep
跟踪我们可以保持的客户
track of them actually why do we have to
跟踪他们实际上为什么我们必须
keep track of them let's make spring
跟踪它们，让我们发春
keep track of it so we just create the
跟踪它，所以我们只创建
client as a component we we have now
客户作为我们的组成部分
interesting capabilities at endpoint
端点的有趣功能
that's a proprietary annotation that
这是一个专有注释
actually happens to be a qualifier that
实际上恰好是一个预选赛
allows us to have multiple work targets
允许我们有多个工作目标
because an application doesn't talk to
因为应用程序不与
one it talks to multiple and you can see
它与多个对话，您可以看到
that service name in there what that
该服务名称在那里
does it actually gives us a locator
它真的给我们一个定位器吗
inside the configuration so you can go
里面的配置，所以你可以去
to your remote configuration and you can
到您的远程配置，您可以
say myself service dot HTTP dot request
说自己服务点HTTP点请求
timeout and it happens to be 200
超时，刚好是200
milliseconds well you can go to the
毫秒，你可以去
remote system and you can say I want it
远程系统，你可以说我想要它
now to be 500 milliseconds push the
现在要500毫秒
configuration out into production and do
配置出产并做
not have to restart the application we
不必重启应用程序
do this with very sophisticated scope
在非常复杂的范围内执行此操作
boxing be in factory post processors
装箱在工厂后处理器中
locate this injection points and we
找到这个注射点，我们
handle everything under the cover that's
处理所有被掩盖的事情
the power of spring it also allow us to
春天的力量也使我们能够
give plug ability to our consumers so
为我们的消费者提供插件功能
for example we have we have a waiting to
例如，我们有一个等待
which like to we like to log our
喜欢我们喜欢登录我们的
transactions coming in but the component
交易进入但组件
that logs that has a exposes an
具有暴露的日志
interface through what we call a SPI and
通过我们称为SPI的接口
if a customer wants to write their own
如果客户想写自己的
they can they just mark their thing as a
他们可以将自己的东西标记为
component as a beam you can say add
可以说是梁的组件
component and they said I primary and
组件，他们说我主要和
all of a sudden we pick that up instead
突然间，我们取而代之
of the other one or the default one and
另一个或默认之一
voila you can plug your own logger more
瞧，您可以插入更多自己的记录器
and more interesting we can do the same
更有趣的是我们可以做同样的事情
with the the underlying HTTP client for
与基础HTTP客户端
the web target nobody does it because
网络目标没有人这样做，因为
who wants to write a brand new HTTP
谁想要写一个全新的HTTP
client and brain instrumental but we
客户和大脑的工具，但我们
have the ability to swap clients on the
有能力交换客户
on the fly so you're still using the web
快速运行，因此您仍在使用网络
target API but you can use Apache or you
目标API，但您可以使用Apache或
can use async HTTP client or finagle or
可以使用异步HTTP客户端或Finagle或
rx native you whatever as long as you as
只要您愿意，rx就可以使您本地化
long as you provide a couple api's and
只要您提供几个api和
you override those beans with a primary
您可以使用主变量覆盖这些bean
we pick them up you don't have to do
我们把它们捡起来，你不必做
anything so now that we have all of this
现在，我们有了所有这些
power we started looking at oh sorry one
威力我们开始关注哦对不起
more thing as much as back in the 90s
可以追溯到90年代
people loved XML we didn't like it we
人们喜欢XML，但我们不喜欢它
hated it
讨厌它
we started with a very modern spring
我们从一个非常现代的春天开始
version so we said zero XML nothing that
版本，所以我们说零XML没什么
comes from the framework requires XML
来自框架需要XML
yet of course for those people that
当然，对于那些
carries that care for XML and love it
怀着对XML的厚爱并喜欢它
we're gonna let them use it so we have
我们要让他们使用它，所以我们有
component based design a lot of these
基于组件的设计很多
smarts that we can do by materializing
通过实现可以实现的智慧
beans with spring and now we found very
豆与春天，现在我们发现
very powerful tool we can compose this
我们可以组成非常强大的工具
into functional profiles and we decided
进入功能配置文件，我们决定
to use a term profile and the profile is
使用术语配置文件，该配置文件是
nothing but a palm that brings all the
只不过带了所有东西的手掌
components together and gives you a
组件在一起，为您提供
slice of functionality so for example
功能切片，例如
this one says I would like to build rest
这个说我想休息
services but I want to have all the
服务，但我想拥有所有
bells and whistles to make them paypal
钟声和口哨声使他们成为贝宝
as a service that's what people stands
作为人们所接受的服务
for compact compatible well maybe you
为了紧凑兼容，也许你
don't want to do a PayPal as a service
不想将PayPal做为服务
thing maybe just want a regular rest
可能只是想定期休息
because it's internal you don't care
因为它是内部的，您不在乎
there's a profile that is called raised
有一个叫做提高的个人资料
profile PayPal it gives you all the
配置文件贝宝它给你所有的
PayPal instrumentation but you don't
PayPal工具，但您没有
have the extra lots of security and all
具有额外的安全性和所有
the other things that that are required
其他所需的东西
for to survive on the peepers side of
为了在偷窥者那边生存
the house maybe you don't want
房子，也许你不想
instrumentation we have a profile called
仪器，我们有一个配置文件称为
rest services and all the DOS is
休息服务，所有的DOS是
basically using integrated rustici with
基本上使用集成Rustica
with the framework and with all the
与框架和所有
bells and whistles but without any
钟声和口哨声，但没有任何
paypal essence we discovered this to be
贝宝的本质，我们发现这是
a very very powerful now for those of
对于那些
you that are spring boot that sounds
你是 spring boot ，听起来
very familiar right
非常熟悉的权利
but this was before we had spring blue
但这是在我们春暖花开之前
so we were already heading in that
所以我们已经在前进
direction couple rules for you can bring
您可以带来方向夫妇规则
a profile anytime you want but rules for
您可以随时访问个人资料，但需要
ourselves was minimum to zero
我们自己从零到零
configuration only really configure what
配置只真正配置什么
make me the customer configure what they
让我让客户配置他们所需要的
really need to do like like for example
确实需要像
a route like we cannot discover things
像我们找不到东西的路线
for them yet make it super flexible so
对他们来说却使它变得超级灵活
that they can actually have nuts and
他们实际上可以有坚果和
bolts all over the place if they want to
如果他们想的话，到处都是螺栓
change things and this actually proved
改变事情，这实际上证明了
to be very successful we release this in
为了取得成功，我们在
I think the first release through 2015
我认为2015年之前的第一个版本
we had great adoption great success on
我们在
duplicating the old frameworks so we're
复制旧框架，所以我们
very successful but a couple problems
非常成功，但有几个问题
start emerging we had people that wanted
开始出现我们有想要的人
to create batch jobs well the spring
在春季良好地创建批处理作业
batch another team took it kind of work
批另一个团队进行了类似的工作
on it and now we notice that the
在它上面，现在我们注意到
frameworks were slightly different so
框架略有不同，所以
now we're going back to this place where
现在我们要回到这个地方
we have multiple ways of doing things
我们有多种做事方式
yet the same name of the framework
框架名称相同
that's weird
这很奇怪
we have people
我们有人
just don't care about rest they want to
只是不在乎他们想休息
do messaging on by the way they're doing
用他们正在做的方式进行消息传递
messaging why do they have to have
消息为什么他们必须有
Tomcat why are we doing a war file for
Tomcat为什么我们要为
them they don't want that they is just a
他们他们不希望他们只是一个
waste we had a group of team we have a
浪费我们有一个团队，我们有一个
team inside the payment space that it
团队内部的支付空间
wants to innovate with some other
想要与其他人一起创新
technologies including Cupid and Lmax
丘比特和Lmax等技术
disruptor
破坏者
they don't want an extra threats they
他们不想要额外的威胁
don't want they don't want Tomcat they
不想他们不想Tomcat
don't want to be a war so we always kind
不想参加战争，所以我们总是友善
of sort of had a soft spot for spring
对春天情有独钟
food and we want to take a look and the
食物，我们想看看和
more we went into the success of the
更我们成功的
adoption we started noticing these
我们开始注意到这些
problems our profiles the work great
问题我们的个人资料工作很棒
that were successful but then we started
那是成功的，但是我们开始了
warning to some of the issues were you
警告某些问题是你
know maven takes you up to a certain
知道maven可以带您达到一定的目标
point and gives you so much tooling but
点，并为您提供了很多工具，但
then things that are like hey in the
然后像嘿的东西
presence of this class I really don't
我真的没有这个班级的存在
want to go this way I want to go this
想走这边我想走这边
other way well you cannot do that with
否则，您将无法做到这一点
with profiles or without configuration
有配置文件或无配置
beans it's really hard so with that I
豆真的很难，所以我
thank you very much so as it was said so
真的很谢谢你
far as he explains the history we went
据他解释我们去的历史
through since the beginning with our
自从我们开始以来
very first frameworks and to to the
最初的框架
moment we where we had job applications
当我们有工作申请的那一刻
in a cloud environment you saw that we
在云环境中，您看到我们
were already able to have a very very
已经能够拥有一个非常非常
robust and functional solution but at
功能强大且功能强大的解决方案
that moment we still didn't have spring
那一刻我们仍然没有春天
good for example we were using spring
很好，例如我们使用弹簧
but we didn't have spring good we were
但是我们没有春天的美好
in cloud we have our own proprietary
在云中，我们拥有自己的专有
path solution we were able to deliver
我们能够提供的路径解决方案
most of the requirements we had
我们拥有的大多数要求
gratefully and especially security we
非常感谢，特别是我们的安全
were able to monitor our applications in
能够监控我们的应用程序
production etc etc etc right so having
生产等等等，所以有
said that why would you want to go one
说，你为什么要去一个
step further introduce a big
一步进一步介绍大
take that risk if everything is seems to
如果一切似乎都冒险
be okay right now right so as you said
现在就可以了，就像你说的那样
in the very beginning I'm from Brazil
一开始我来自巴西
and there we have this huge soccer
那里有这个巨大的足球
culture and in Portuguese we say that
文化和葡萄牙语，我们说
sister Jimmy tuganda porque vas a mu
姐姐吉米·图加达·波克瓦斯·穆
Daria and that means if your thing is
达里亚（Daria），这意味着如果你的事情是
winning why would you change it right
赢了，为什么你会改变它正确
well we don't know if it's all what
好吧，我们不知道是不是全部
happened the last World Cup so we had to
上届世界杯​​发生了，所以我们不得不
go beyond and we have to really
超越，我们必须真正
anticipate issues we have to be
预测我们必须要解决的问题
visionaries and we have also to be smart
有远见的人，我们也必须聪明
enough to look at other people what they
足以看别人
are doing and learn with that not just
在做和学习，而不仅仅是
with our mistakes but with successful
犯错但成功
coming from other organizations right
来自其他组织的权利
and that's what we decide to do at that
这就是我们决定要做的
particular moment even though we were a
即使我们是一个特殊的时刻
rat evolving we wanted to go beyond and
老鼠进化，我们想超越
Springwood was not just a bird board
斯普林伍德不只是一个鸟板
person but like a guard explained
人，但像一个警卫解释
something that was a rat naturally
自然是老鼠的东西
converging in our path and we wanted to
融合在我们的道路上，我们想
explore we wanted to see what that was
探索我们想看看那是什么
about but the very first thing I
关于但我的第一件事
realized was that the solution we had in
意识到我们所拥有的解决方案
place our framework was a rat a little
放置我们的框架有点麻烦
similar to it Springwood and it was our
类似于Springwood，这是我们的
touch a few of these points so for
触摸这些要点，以便
example the way to turn a regular
例举常规的方式
application into a paper wrapped
申请成纸包装
application was by this very initial
最初的申请是
step which is your parent in your
这是你的父母
profile your maven profile and that
分析您的Maven个人资料，然后
would not just bring you some some
不仅会给你带来一些
dependence management for example much
依赖管理例如
more than that we already had this
不仅如此，我们已经有了这个
notion of trying to anticipate all the
试图预见所有
dependencies you would bring and avoid
您将带来并避免的依赖
conflicts etc but more than that like
冲突等，但不仅如此
the profiles
个人资料
Edoardo explained and they're very
爱德华多解释说，他们非常
similar to spring with starters but not
类似于带有启动器的弹簧，但不
as powerful as a spring with starters
像初学者一样强大
they are much more powerful Springs boot
他们更强大的Springs启动
starters all this noise
使所有这些声音发声
of an opinionated framework that's able
有思想的框架
to be aware of your application the
要知道您的应用程序
charge you have the properties you have
收取您拥有的财产
and all their all these criterias who
他们所有这些标准是谁
then automatically configure your
然后自动配置您的
application we didn't have that and we
应用程序，我们没有那个，我们
of course we were amazed to see that
当然，我们很惊讶地看到
happening and we wanted to take
发生了，我们想采取
advantage of that as well when comes to
当谈到
ops and removing that gap between us and
行动并消除我们与
then we already had in place many
那么我们已经有很多
solutions for metrics and monitoring but
指标和监控解决方案，但
it was really good to see that
真的很高兴看到
Springwood and the whole spring gecko
斯普林伍德和整个春天的壁虎
system also had other options that were
系统还具有其他选择
right there many of them even better
就在那里，其中许多甚至更好
than ours and they came for free I mean
比我们的免费，我的意思是免费
in terms of maintenance we don't have
就维护而言，我们没有
too much cost anymore right since spring
自春季以来，成本太高了
wood is already providing that so we
木头已经提供了，所以我们
wanted to take advantage of all of that
想要利用所有这些优势
and we I'm not even talking about all
而且我什至不谈论所有
these other great great features that
这些其他伟大的功能
you all have heard about have seen and I
你们都听说过
probably using a read like us right so
可能使用像我们这样的读物吧
we want to use all that we own paper
我们想用我们所有的纸
applications to use all of that so we
应用程序使用所有这些，所以我们
decided to introduce a spring boot at
决定在
PayPal and that journey is started
贝宝，旅程就此开始
around October last year as a proof of
作为去年十月的证明
concept first and now we are here right
概念，现在我们在这里
well a few more reasons to you about
还有更多关于您的理由
spring boot that I wanted to share with
我想分享的 spring boot
you so first we wanted to have a lighter
你，所以我们首先要打火机
container the whole notion of embedded
容器整个嵌入式概念
container to us that made a lot of sense
对我们来说很有意义的容器
because we were already in the cloud and
因为我们已经在云端
we wanted to be more and more aligned
我们希望越来越团结
with the this idea of a lighter
这个打火机的想法
application on microspheres and we also
在微球上的应用，我们也
wanted to experiment with different
想尝试不同的
containers we didn't want to have that
我们不想拥有的容器
as another impediment or another
作为另一个障碍或另一个
roadblock in terms of maintaining that
维护的障碍
or even the
甚至
to our fast solution so we wanted the
快速的解决方案，所以我们想要
container to be there for us and do what
容器在那里为我们做些什么
supposed to do but not at a very high
应该做，但不是很高
price besides that the same situation
价格一样的情况
applies to the development experience
适用于开发经验
right you sit in your laptop and
你坐在笔记本电脑上
developing an application you also don't
开发您也不需要的应用程序
want to have I stand alone tone cat or
想让我独自站立
whatever application server server
任何应用程序服务器服务器
continuous hub and then you have to tie
连续的集线器，然后您必须绑
that to your IDE and then you have that
到你的IDE，然后你有
problem of synchronizing code etcetera
同步代码等问题
etcetera etc we want simplicity right we
etcetera等我们想要简单吧
want to reduce maintenance and cost so
想减少维护和成本，所以
all of that was important besides
所有这些都很重要
aligning with spring would start with
与春天对齐将开始于
spring frameworks that we were already
我们已经存在的春季框架
using we use for example spring
使用我们使用例如春天
integration spring batch for for
的集成弹簧批处理
depending on the type of application use
取决于应用程序的使用类型
and many other spring frameworks we also
还有许多其他的Spring框架
use docker and we are going towards a
使用泊坞窗，我们正朝着
hybrid cloud solution - so all of that
混合云解决方案-所有这些
made sense and we were we were ok I
有道理，我们当时我们还好我
think it's the right decision to go this
认为这样做是正确的决定
way but it was not straightforward it
方式，但不是那么简单
was not that easy maybe this is the most
不是那么容易，也许这是最
important information we'd like to share
我们想分享的重要信息
with you today I don't know if you are
今天和你在一起我不知道你是否
going to throw something similar or not
会抛出类似或不相似的东西
in your your company but we faced some
在贵公司，但是我们遇到了一些
challenge and the very first one
挑战和第一个挑战
realized was there was no rest easy
意识到没有轻松的休息
spring boot starter available at that
春季启动启动器可用
time and why is that important well I
时间，为什么那很重要？
suppose it's very common for spring
假设春天很普通
applications to use spring MVC or spring
使用spring MVC或spring的应用程序
data resurrect but we are not doing that
数据复活，但我们没有这样做
maybe two years ago over a little over
大概两年前
that we decided to evaluate what would
我们决定评估什么
be the better way to provide a rest
是更好的休息方式
infrastructure and we also we
基础设施，我们也
wanted to adhere to this back at a time
想一次坚持下去
which is jax-rs so we evaluated a few
这是jax-rs，所以我们评估了一些
jax-rs implementations besides trying to
jax-rs实现，除了尝试
decide the best one we also wanted to
决定我们也想做的最好的
align with that and make sure our
与之保持一致，并确保我们
framework would fit together with that
框架将适合
too right and the chosen one was rest
太正确了，选择的一个就休息了
easy for many reasons many many reasons
由于许多原因而容易许多原因
we already knew sex that very well at
我们已经很了解性
the time because that that's the one
时间，因为那是那个
used by our legacy framework and we
由我们的旧框架使用，我们
compared the Jersey and rest easy it
比较球衣和休息容易吗
word to talk about for example being
谈论的词例如
able to plug the HTTP client design
能够插入HTTP客户端设计
using the one in wand we liked a lot the
使用魔杖，我们非常喜欢
API gracias offered we also evaluate
提供的API gracias我们也进行了评估
performance documentation how active the
绩效文件的活跃程度
community behind the open-source project
开源项目背后的社区
was all of that and recipes was a
就是所有这些，而食谱是
solution that we like better right
我们更喜欢的解决方案
jax-rs based two years pass by now we
基于jax-rs的两年过去了
are going to the spring woodland and
要去春季林地，
there is no a spring boot starter so
没有弹簧启动器，所以
what you do we decided then to develop
您做什么我们决定然后发展
the rest easy starter and we did and
其余的简单入门，我们做到了
we've open first that you talk a little
我们先打开您再说一点
bit more about that later second
稍后再说一点
challenge servlet container
挑战servlet容器
customization we are using Tomcat
我们正在使用Tomcat进行定制
Eduardo mention secured right very very
爱德华多（Eduardo）非常非常提到担保权
important requirement for paper
纸张的重要要求
applications so we had some specific
应用程序，所以我们有一些特定的
customizations we had to do at the
我们必须在
container level container the connectors
容器级容器的连接器
for example and thankfully at that time
举例来说，幸运的是当时
Tomcat had a very nice documented API
Tomcat有一个非常好的文档化API
that we could use of course it was not a
我们可以使用的当然不是
standard had nothing to do with the
标准与
servlet spec or any it was for Puteri I
servlet规范或任何适用于Puteri I的规范
mean it was the specific to don't care
表示无关紧要
well as we moved to a spring boot that's
以及当我们转到 spring boot 时
gone that does not exist anymore because
不存在了，因为
now Tomcat is just a jar in your
现在Tomcat只是您的一个罐子
application right there's any other one
申请还有其他
so the whole API is gone as well that
所以整个API也都消失了
does not mean we could not address our
并不意味着我们无法解决我们的问题
needs we still good and thanks for
需要我们仍然很好，谢谢
spring wood because
春天木因为
at the low level it also provides a very
在低水平它也提供了一个非常
nice programmatic API so that you can
不错的程序化API，因此您可以
customize your container I don't know if
自定义您的容器，我不知道
you have used that or if you're familiar
您已经使用过或者如果您熟悉
of that well yes it's true and it's
是的，是的，这是真的
amazing we could do everything we used
神奇的是我们可以做所有我们使用过的
to do before now we can still do the
现在要做，我们仍然可以
lifecycle and the face all of that is
生命周期和面对的一切
different we are going to talk about
我们将要讨论的不同
that in a second but we still could
一秒钟，但我们仍然可以
address our needs
满足我们的需求
well I forgot to press the button that's
好吧，我忘了按下
the tomcat API or the UML lollipop
Tomcat API或UML棒棒糖
notation you know if you are for me
符号，你知道你是否适合我
looked at yes so now talking about
看着是的，所以现在谈论
initialization right here we have a very
初始化在这里，我们有一个非常
nice diagram on the left side you see
您在左侧看到的漂亮图表
before on the right side you see after
之前在右侧，您看到之后
before spring boot after spring boot at
在春季引导之前在春季引导之后
PayPal frameworks so notice that you
贝宝框架，请注意
have four layers right there right the
有四层就在那里
one let's let's start by the left side
让我们从左侧开始
the other one Tomcat that used to be our
另一个曾经是我们的Tomcat
container it is - but it was not
容器-是的，但不是
embedded it was a standalone regular
嵌入它是一个独立的常规
Tomcat inside of it we had our raptor
里面有雄猫，我们有猛禽
framework the paypal framework spring
框架，贝宝框架，春季
and then the application it's like a
然后应用程序就像
Russian doll right now let's take a look
俄罗斯娃娃现在让我们看一下
at the right side there is modest tall
在右边有个矮小的个子
that does not open itself inside of all
不会在所有内部打开自己
the others his application is too right
其他人他的申请太正确了
but now Tomcat is the second smallest
但是现在Tomcat是第二小的
one you see it inverted and spring is
一个你看到它倒立，春天是
now the very first one the biggest one
现在第一个最大的
outside and raptor is this - the second
外面和猛禽是这个-第二
the yellow layer right there this issue
黄色层就在那里这个问题
the second so again I don't know if you
第二次，所以我不知道你是否
have gone through some something similar
经历了一些类似的事情
to this in your organization but that
在您的组织中，但是
was a very very important realization we
是非常非常重要的认识
had this is something that you don't see
这是你看不到的东西
I don't know I don't think you'll see
我不知道我不认为你会看到
when you're just developing an
当你正在开发一个
application or especially a application
应用程序，特别是应用程序
from scratch
从头开始
we're dealing with a whole framework
我们正在处理整个框架
that you want to offer so that business
您想提供的东西
units can beauty applications this was
单位可以美容应用，这是
very key so the initialization order and
非常关键，所以初始化顺序和
who manages that it's completely
谁管理的完全是
different now before it was Tomcat right
Tomcat出现之前，现在有所不同
now it's spring in Tomcat which it's in
现在是在Tomcat中的春天
compliance with the servlets back you
遵守servlet可以支持您
have this notion of a servlet container
具有servlet容器的概念
initializer application type and
初始化应用程序类型和
interface right which happens to have
恰好具有的接口权限
this a notation called handle types and
这就是句柄类型和
that is triggered very very earlier
这是很早触发的
during the bootstrap of your application
在您的应用程序引导期间
and that's very powerful gives you a
这非常强大，为您提供了
chance to do many things earlier and
有机会尽早做很多事情，
manage your application right that's
管理您的申请权
gone and we were using that with rather
走了，我们正在用它
a lot we have to have many components we
很多我们必须有很多组件
wanted to configure and initialize
想配置和初始化
earlier configuration security etcetera
较早的配置安全性等
that are logging all of that was
记录了所有的
completely out of place well the good
完全错位好
news though is that spring is the one in
新闻是春天是其中的一个
that position right now and we we really
现在的位置，我们真的
trust that it was just a matter of time
相信这只是时间问题
adjusting these building blocks to get
调整这些构件以获得
to the same result you want and that
达到您想要的结果，并且
that was the case so we did all these
就是这样，所以我们做了所有这些
modifications and everything worked well
修改，一切正常
later
后来
server container configuration we talked
我们谈论的服务器容器配置
about customization now configuration
关于立即定制配置
well you should have this XML file for
好吧，您应该拥有此XML文件
Tomcat before now it's gone good news
Tomcat之前已经消失了好消息
this is praying good also provides
这是祈祷的美好，也提供
everything you need in that sense it's
从这个意义上讲，您需要的一切
either via your property file your
通过您的财产文件
application the properties or whatever
应用属性或其他
it's named or programmatically so again
还是以编程方式命名
was something we had to do and there was
这是我们必须要做的事，
no gap there Springwood offered all all
那里没有空隙，斯普林伍德提供了所有
the the hooks the integration points the
集成的钩子指向
API we needed to make things is moved
我们需要使事物移动的API
especially when you think about backward
特别是当你想到倒退
compatibility right Eduardo mentioned
提到爱德华多的兼容权
that that's very important very very
那非常重要
important you cannot introduce something
重要的是你不能介绍一些东西
that's amazing beautiful and new and
那是惊人的美丽和新颖，
modern if the curse to get there is too
如果到达那里的诅咒也太现代了
much or if you break you just break make
很多，或者如果你打破了，那就打破了
it impossible to to chop great skinny
不可能切成薄片
jar approach when you think about
考虑时使用jar方法
delivery you might think well let's have
您可能认为很好的交付方式
just one jar of fetch our jar contains
一罐取来的罐子里
orders and that's the recommended way of
订单，这是推荐的方式
delivering your application when you go
外出时交付您的申请
to the documentation right Springwood
在文档右边的Springwood
documentation we decided to do something
我们决定做一些文档
different here why because we decided to
这里不同，为什么，因为我们决定
take a look at how things happen behind
看一下事情如何发生
the scenes and we realize that we spring
场景，我们意识到我们春天
introduced this custom closed loader and
介绍了这个定制的封闭式装载机，并
which of course it's great and works etc
当然哪个很棒并且可以用，等等
but bring some extra complexity okay and
但是带来一些额外的复杂性
what's the benefit of having a fetch our
取回我们有什么好处
or is a Qdoba jar if in our case at
还是Qdoba罐子，如果在我们的情况下
least in the end of the day the
至少在一天结束时
developer will not really touch that we
开发人员不会真正感动我们
had this past solution we had this
有了过去的解决方案，我们有了这个
deployment engine and everything was
部署引擎，一切都过去了
automated so it was like okay here to
自动化，所以在这里感觉还可以
you a nice feature but it's complex
您的功能不错，但很复杂
comes with this risk but
伴随着这种风险，但
are not really taking advantage of the
并没有真正利用
benefits so we decided to not do it we
好处，所以我们决定不这样做，我们
decided to do it
决定这样做
to make it simpler we are same about
为了简化起见，我们是一样的
that by ourselves and we have a way to
靠我们自己，我们有办法
lay our files and folders and everything
放置我们的文件和文件夹以及所有内容
but we are keeping the class holders in
但是我们把班级持有人留在
the way that we want and in the end of
我们想要的方式并最终
the day the solution works the same the
解决方案相同的日期
Maven plug in Springwood has to run your
Maven插件必须运行Springwood
applications is still available works
应用程序仍然可用
fine in developing environment
在开发环境中很好
everything is great the IDE you have is
一切都很棒，您拥有的IDE是
also great to to do whatever you want we
做任何您想做的事也很棒
are idea agnostic by the way so that's
顺便说一句，这个想法不可知
just something we wanted to mention that
只是我们想提的一点
we also evaluated and why we chose the
我们还评估了为什么我们选择了
solution we chose the decision which was
解决方案，我们选择的决定是
J max conflict we have we had a few
我们有几个最大冲突
conflicts when comes to JMX we were
JMX发生冲突时，我们
using we use a lot of J max any spring
使用我们在任何春季都使用大量的J max
would also like to MX and tries to go
也想MX并尝试去
one step ahead and have some J max
领先一步，有一些J max
registrations and beans etc done for you
注册和Bean等为您完成
automatically that's great but it
自动，那很棒，但是
conflicted with what we had in place so
与我们所拥有的相抵触
we also had to do with some
我们还与一些
modifications but again nothing low
修改，但再次没什么低
level nothing scary now just searching
级别没有什么吓人的，现在只是搜索
the commutation spring book
通勤春季书
documentation and everything we need to
文档以及我们需要的一切
make everything happy was right there
让一切都开心就在那里
so nothing nothing bad here nani process
所以这里没什么不好的纳尼过程
yeah we use on any process to make sure
是的，我们在任何过程中都使用以确保
our application is gracefully restarted
我们的应用正常启动
whenever necessary
必要时
etc etc well before we had a regular
等等等等，直到我们有一个常规
standalone tomcat container now we don't
现在我们没有独立的tomcat容器
have that anymore we have a job
有了，我们有了工作
application so was that a real problem
应用程序是一个真正的问题
no it was just something else we had to
不，那只是我们必须要做的
do but not not nothing special no
做但不是没有什么特别的不
blockers there logging
日志记录器有阻塞
similar situations more adjustments and
类似情况下需要更多调整
to be made you don't have Tomcat anymore
使您不再拥有Tomcat
taking care of that at the low level
在低层照顾
against a java application there the
针对那里的Java应用程序
logging changed a little bit log
日志更改了一点日志
locations had to change log locations
位置必须更改日志位置
had to change we are using a solid for J
必须更改，我们为J使用固体
so that was great so that's it now
所以那太好了，就是现在
upgrading it's the last one another
升级是最后一个
lease right very important very very
租赁权非常重要非常非常
part important I don't know if again I
重要的部分，我不知道我是否再次
don't know if you are going through the
不知道你是否正在经历
same thing we did or she already did
我们做过或她已经做过的事情
that or if you're planning to but that
或如果您打算但
item right there is something that it's
右边的东西是
hard to predict in the beginning it's
一开始很难预测
something that you don't face with them
你不面对他们的东西
really really feel that pain as you go
真的很痛苦
through this transition and it's
通过这个过渡，
something you really learn from later at
您以后会从中学到的东西
the later phase where when you finally
后来的阶段，当你最终
have your first applications adopting
让您的第一个应用程序采用
your your new framework we are still
您的新框架，我们仍然
learning we are super improving and we
学习我们正在不断进步，我们
are automating our upgrade okay
正在自动化我们的升级，好吗
we decided that automation was the best
我们认为自动化是最好的
way to do it a manual upgrade is not
手动升级的方法不是
going to scare you
会吓到你
we are writing a to to do so and we are
我们正在写一个这样做，我们是
hoping to chop answers that - I don't
希望砍的答案-我不
know but maybe in the future we can talk
知道，但也许将来我们可以谈谈
about that hopefully and this is a non
关于那个希望，这是一个非
spring boot to springboard transition
弹簧靴到跳板的过渡
right so hopefully more people can can
对，所以希望更多的人可以
use it and contribute and make it better
使用它并做出贡献并使其变得更好
because that I think that is very
因为我认为那是非常
important okay so our wizard seen a few
很重要，所以我们的向导看到了一些
numbers so our very first release was
数字，所以我们的第一个版本是
made available to our applications on
提供给我们的应用程序
April so four months ago and out of 300
大约4个月前的300年四月
raptor applications over 100 are already
猛禽应用程序已超过100
using the spring boot version of it the
使用它的春季启动版本
latest version and we already have
最新版本，我们已经拥有
around 200 million cows per day on
每天约有2亿头奶牛
raptor in Springwood out of 5 billion
斯普林伍德的猛禽中有50亿
you see 4.2 there it's updated it's 5 it
您会看到4.2那里有更新它是5
looks like number from last week to this
看起来像是从上周到现在的数字
week and we got really good feedback
一周，我们得到了很好的反馈
from developers really really good I
来自开发人员真的真的很好我
don't I don't think it's because of buzz
我不认为这是因为嗡嗡声
necessarily it's because of a spring
一定是因为春天
good it's just because of how
好，只是因为
much better experience it brings to the
带来的更好的体验
table to the developer and we want to do
表给开发者，我们要做
the same for ops later we are still
以后的操作也一样
using our proprietary metrics and
使用我们的专有指标
monitoring solutions this is job this is
监控解决方案，这是工作，这是
just like a first phase of how our whole
就像我们整个阶段的第一阶段
transition the next phase will add that
过渡到下一阶段将添加
so now talking about what we had to do
所以现在谈论我们必须要做的
in terms of design as it rather said we
就设计而言，正如我们所说
realized that it would not be very
意识到那不是很
feasible to do demos or show code or
进行演示或显示代码的可行性，或者
anything but this diagram that you can
除了这个图，你可以
see here shows a few blocks the eye
看到这里显示了几眼
starters they are spring boots starters
他们是 spring boot 起动器
okay we realized that it was really
好吧，我们意识到这确实是
really the best thing to do just adopt
真的最好的办法就是采用
this technology and we first of all we
这项技术，我们首先
layered our components in these four
在这四个方面将我们的组件分层
different layers let's start by the
让我们从不同的层次开始
second one actually at PayPal we have
实际上在PayPal的第二个
three types of applications it's either
三种类型的应用程序
a rest application a message demon or a
其余应用程序消息恶魔或
batch application Eduardo red told you
批处理应用程序Eduardo red告诉你
about that rain so we have one spring
关于那场雨，所以我们有了一个春天
boots started for each one and then plus
靴子开始每个人，然后加
two extra four different types of
两个额外的四种不同类型的
flavors of applications there are
有多种应用
additional helper starters let's say
可以说其他辅助启动器
this way and then going back to the
这样，然后回到
first layer a core starter okay that is
第一层是核心入门程序，可以
shared among every single raptor
在每个猛禽之间共享
application this course starter is
此课程入门的应用程序
responsible for things like the whole
对整个事情负责
framework initialization and
框架初始化和
configuration and initializing the
配置并初始化
security and all the components that you
安全性以及您所拥有的所有组件
must have to defines you as a
必须将您定义为
application and then the second third
应用程序，然后是第二个
type the third one and the fourth one
键入第三和第四
pretty much they are clients or drivers
他们几乎是客户或司机
for external systems the third one
对于外部系统，第三个
particularly they are clients for
特别是他们是
downstream services you want to
您想要的下游服务
for example or either our so appropriate
例如，或者我们如此合适
are because we still have these legacy
是因为我们仍然有这些遗产
applications or the latest one in the
应用程序或最新的
newest framework and then the fourth
最新的框架，然后是第四个
layer if you want to integrate with
层，如果您想与
caching or messaging etc or database all
缓存或消息传递等或全部数据库
of dinner starters that means
晚餐开始的意思
configuration now is automated
现在的配置是自动化的
they are opinionated as well we give
他们也很自以为是
some freedom for our applications
我们的应用有一些自由
actually to choose a few third-party
实际上要选择一些第三方
components they want to use and we make
他们想要使用的组件，我们制造
sure all of that's aligned so we use a
确保所有内容都对齐，因此我们使用
lot of those conditional annotations and
许多这些条件注释和
we as a duardo said we also use
我们作为杜阿多（Duardo）说，我们也使用
programmatic ways of registering Dean's
注册Dean的程序化方式
etc etc so that was the biggest effort
等等等，这是最大的努力
we had in terms of coding during this
我们在此期间的编码方面
transition and if you want to calculate
过渡，如果你想计算
about that in person if you want to know
关于这个，如果你想知道
more details now talking about our need
现在更多细节谈论我们的需求
to have rusty Springs boots darker we
使生锈的斯普林斯靴子更黑
also developed that right it's not in
还发展了它不在
the previous diagram it's an open-source
上图是开源的
project now and what it brings to you
现在进行项目，并为您带来什么
well first of all it enables rest easy
首先，它使休息变得轻松
for spring booty applications that was
对于春季战利品应用程序
not possible before it was just not
在不可能之前不可能
possible now it is in addition to that
现在有可能
every single one of your jax-rs resource
您的jax-rs资源的每一个
and providers or even sub resource they
以及提供者甚至子资源
can be spring beans okay that was all
可以是四季豆，好吧，仅此而已
red possible before rust-eze it has the
生锈之前可能有红色
spring bootie integration that was a rad
spring boot 集成，这是一个rad
possible but we made it aligned together
可能，但我们使它对齐
nicely with spring boots as well and
搭配 spring boot 也很不错
this is new now your jax-rs application
这是新的，现在您的jax-rs应用程序
can be found and registered nicely as I
可以找到并很好地注册为我
spring being as well okay this is
春天还可以，这是
something new that they did not exist
他们不存在的新事物
before we also provide other options of
在我们还提供其他选项之前
registration which are more aligned with
更符合的注册
the old days let's say this way and the
过去，我们可以这样说，
jax-rs is back so for example you can do
jax-rs又回来了，例如，您可以
that programmatically or rely on clasp
以编程方式或依靠扣
as a scanning or just have a
作为扫描或只是有一个
configuration file pointing to the class
指向类的配置文件
so we have options right and finally
所以我们有选择权，最后
you're not missing anything if you had a
如果您有一个
previous application that was using
以前使用的应用程序
recision had all those configurations
直肠具有所有这些配置
very nicely defined for you they will be
为您定义的很好，他们将
there is - ok they will still be
有-好的，他们仍然会
available for you and if you have been
适用于您，如果您去过
using wrasses already you know that they
已经使用濑鱼了，你知道他们
are done as servlet context
作为servlet上下文完成
initialization parameters well they are
初始化参数很好
is - available to you
是-可供您使用
in Springwood even though we don't have
在斯普林伍德，即使我们没有
a web XML file anymore in Springwood the
Springwood中的一个Web XML文件
Springwood has a way to define those
斯普林伍德有一种方法来定义那些
properties in your application
应用程序中的属性
properties file we are just using that
属性文件，我们只是在使用
so it's all the same the same thing you
所以你都是一样的东西
do in a regular spring good application
在常规春季做好应用
you also do here for those properties
您也可以在这里为这些物业
here you can see just an example of what
在这里您可以看到一个例子
your application class would look like
您的应用程序类看起来像
so everything you do it there is you
所以你所做的一切就是你
just add a component a notation now it's
只需在组件上添加一个符号即可
spring thing and it will be available
春天的东西，它将可用
for you your your mapping will work fine
对你来说，你的映射可以正常工作
you have a server behind the same
您在同一台服务器后面
serving your request etc it's an open
满足您的要求，这是一个开放的
source project if you want to check it
源项目是否要检查
out
出
that's the URL it's you can just go to
这就是URL，您可以直接转到
github PayPal you see all our
github PayPal，您将看到我们所有的
open-source projects we have many and
开源项目，我们有很多
one of them is this one and if you like
其中之一就是这个，如果你喜欢
it please start our project alright so
它请开始我们的项目
where we want to go now again this is
我们现在想去的地方是
just the beginning there's just so much
仅仅是开始，有这么多
to be done so much to be adopted from
要做很多事情以被采纳
Springwood and so much so many lessons
斯普林伍德和这么多的课程
as well personally Eduardo and I got
以及我个人的爱德华多
being here and taking a look at spring
在这里，看看春天
cloud and even Cloud Foundry and all
云，甚至是Cloud Foundry等
these things talking to other frogs so
这些东西和其他青蛙说话
the very first thing we want to do is we
我们要做的第一件事就是
want to introduce this concept of Raptor
想介绍一下猛禽的概念
light so right now if you are a PayPal
如果您是贝宝，请立即点亮
developer depending on the type of
开发者取决于类型
application you have you bring this
你有这个应用程序
Raptor flavored framework for you and
Raptor风格的框架为您和
there you go you do whatever you want
你去那里你想做什么
however we realize that that's not
但是我们意识到那不是
really really ideal for a few situations
在某些情况下真的非常理想
we have for example many business units
例如，我们有许多业务部门
and they are so big that they have their
他们是如此之大，以至于他们拥有自己的
own infrastructure Kings
自己的基础设施之王
internally for example risk management
内部，例如风险管理
let's just mention this one or payments
让我们只说这一项或付款
there are many right so they were like
有很多权利，所以他们就像
okay we want to use raptor but there was
好吧，我们想使用猛禽，但是
something you an extra layer we want to
您想要我们增加的一层
add right there to offer to our
在此处添加要提供给我们的权利
developers and it would be better if
开发人员，如果
rapper was flexible for that because i
说唱歌手很灵活，因为我
want to be able to have better
希望能够变得更好
customization so that's what raptor like
定制，这就是猛禽喜欢的
is it's a minimal Springwood paper
这是最小的斯普林伍德纸吗
application to add something order and
应用程序添加一些命令和
we won't allow basically the java
我们基本上不允许Java
container that's it so right now we
容器就是这样，我们现在
talked about oh you can create a service
谈到哦，你可以创建一个服务
or a message demon what if you want to
或消息恶魔，如果你想
clear the command-line interface we used
清除我们使用的命令行界面
to want to use all the paypal
想要使用所有的贝宝
infrastructure Oh spring boots perfect
基础设施哦， spring boot 完美
for that
为了那个原因
there's no reason why we cannot do that
没有理由为什么我们不能那样做
so we're gonna create a very minimum
所以我们要创建一个最小的
core that just gives you all the paypal
只给您所有支付宝的核心
core services and then you can actually
核心服务，然后您实际上可以
start creating on top of that yeah and
在那边开始创作
that would you still give you security
那你还会给你安全吗
for example which is something very
例如这是非常
important again we are going to start a
同样重要的是，我们将开始
new face to go and take advantage of
要去利用新面孔
more spring good stuff and here just a
春天的好东西，这里只是一个
few of simple examples of them that we
我们几个简单的例子
are not really using yet but you do like
尚未真正使用，但您确实喜欢
to
至
and also this next little piece of items
还有这下一个小项目
here they bring technology that we
他们带来的技术
already have in place we are at using
已经在使用中了
analog technology but we would like to
模拟技术，但我们希望
evaluate others other options right so
正确评估其他选项
for example undertow instead of Tomcat
例如undertow而不是Tomcat
especially for performance reasons but
特别是出于性能原因，但是
if you have to evaluate and see what
如果您必须评估，看看有什么
what it takes to go there right I was
我去那里需要什么
very excited about the kingdom when they
当他们对王国感到非常兴奋
took spring 5 going with reactor as the
花了5号弹簧和反应堆一起
caucuses like oh I don't have to work on
像哦，因为我不必工作
this too much
这个太多了
okay probably just working but we
好吧，也许只是工作，但我们
actually had that in our writer we want
实际上在我们的作家中有我们想要的
to try to go into an on servlet model
尝试进入on servlet模型
for the exact same reasons that were
出于完全相同的原因
presented in the in the keynote we wanna
在我们想要的主题演讲中提出
we want to love people to create a
我们想爱人们创造一个
synchronous non-blocking services and
同步非阻塞服务和
right now we have the the servlet model
现在我们有了servlet模型
that is kind of holding us back on there
有点让我们回到那里
yeah
是的
that's great you definitely take a look
太好了，你一定要看看
at that it's spring cloud configuration
那是春天的云配置
so like we said earlier in the talk we
就像我们刚才在谈话中所说的
are I do that we already have a remote
我是不是已经有一个遥控器了
configuration system in place but that's
配置系统到位，但这就是
proprietary so there are two things you
专有的，所以您有两件事
could do we could just go and take
可以做，我们可以去拿
advantage of khonsu or or the github
khonsu或github的优势
approach that iSpring boot applications
iSpring启动应用程序的方法
have now or we could just do a half step
现在或者我们可以做半个步骤
which is okay let's reuse the api the
没关系，让我们重新使用api
configuration api that's right there
正确的配置API
because we're not we're not even using
因为我们不是，我们甚至都没有使用
that the notion of the Refresh scope and
刷新范围的概念和
configuration properties annotations and
配置属性注释和
tied that 12-hour solution we have all
捆绑了12小时的解决方案
that concepts through a proprietary api
通过专有API的概念
it's actually uses the Apache Commons
它实际上是使用Apache Commons
configuration API so it's not like that
配置API，所以不是那样
poor Puteri yeah would it be great if we
可怜的普特里是的，如果我们
could actually hook up and switch and
实际上可以挂接并切换，
use our system with those capabilities
通过这些功能使用我们的系统
on the backend would still use the
在后端仍然会使用
spring annotations like add refresh
春天注释，例如添加刷新
configuration and all of that stuff so
配置以及所有这些东西
that's something that was very
那是非常
interesting I wanna explore yeah served
有趣的我想探索
service discovery same thing we all have
服务发现我们都拥有同样的东西
a solution in place but we're like wow
一个合适的解决方案，但我们就像哇
there's so many other nice options right
还有很多其他不错的选择
there out there right we had to take a
在那里，我们不得不采取一个
look at those two and you talk about the
看看那两个，你谈论
last I think yeah we have some needs for
最后，我认为是的，我们有一些需求
high performance and I think there was a
高性能，我认为有一个
talk yesterday that talked about when
昨天聊到说什么时候
you have micro services and you go to
你有微服务，你去
what's close and dear to you which is
与您最亲近的是
HTTP not necessarily the best for
HTTP不一定最适合
multi-hop and multi service
多跳多服务
communication pretty slow so we want to
沟通很慢，所以我们想
explore with that was a very interesting
进行探索非常有趣
talk about Google RPC yesterday that
昨天谈到Google RPC
looked very interesting we're already
看起来很有趣，我们已经
using protobuf in some in some domains
在某些领域中使用Protobuf
so that would be kind of connects phase
所以这将是一种连接阶段
there's Aaron which is another protocol
还有亚伦这是另一个协议
that looks very interesting to play with
看起来很有趣
and of course AMQP
当然还有AMQP
rabitor Cupid will have been playing for
狂人丘比特将一直为
with this with that yeah we are open for
有了这个，我们愿意
questions
问题
yes
是
would you mind repeating the question
你介意重复这个问题吗
oh the question was if in 2014 we
哦，问题是2014年
started with back-end as a service
从后端即服务开始
the 2014 was modernized the Java
2014年对Java进行了现代化
developments so we could have a micro
发展，所以我们可以有一个微观
service style architecture heading
服务风格架构标题
towards that so we don't a lot of our
为此，我们没有很多
back-end services we're already
后端服务，我们已经
following it so our model so they're
跟随我们的模型，所以他们
already services there's a service
已经服务有服务
registry we have enterprise interfaces
注册表我们有企业接口
that you have to do a lot of that has a
你必须要做的很多事
this proprietary protocol so you cannot
这个专有协议，所以您不能
just go and grab jax-ws and use it let
只是去抓住jax-ws并使用它
me quickly so the question was how do we
我很快，所以问题是我们如何
do it do you see that boxes so a client
你看到那个盒子了吗
that's the guy that allows us to to talk
那是允许我们交谈的人
to those back-end services so it still
那些后端服务，所以它仍然
presents itself as a regular RPC like
表现为常规的RPC之类的
you inject the you inject the act we
你注入你注入我们的行为
made it virtually did a couple tricks
使它实际上做了几个技巧
there we actually still we did a sliding
在那里，我们实际上仍然在滑动
of that protocol on top of jax-rs
该协议在jax-rs之上的
because at the end of the day jack
因为在一天结束时杰克
service is just a post and we just get
服务只是一个职位，我们得到
data so we use a lot of the hook and
数据，所以我们使用了大量的钩子和
then we we can inject the enterprise
然后我们可以注入企业
interface which is generated which is an
生成的接口是
an annotated jax-rs interface
带注释的jax-rs接口
we don't have a lot of soap based
我们没有很多肥皂
services internally it's about this
内部服务就是关于这个
proprietary protocol and we had for
专有协议，我们有
adoption purposes we have actually also
我们实际上也有采用的目的
done the service side of it we
完成了服务方面的工作
discourage it but you can actually
阻止它，但是你实际上可以
implement services of this type inside
在内部实施此类服务
the new stack we don't have that slide
没有幻灯片的新堆栈
but yeah I mean it's easier transition
但是，是的，我的意思是过渡更容易
this but like what fabulous all right
但这就像什么神话般的好吧
it's not just about bringing the new and
这不只是带来新的
yay we have to adapt to what's out there
是的，我们必须适应那里的情况
yeah so it's very good question
是的，这是一个很好的问题
don't repeat the question the question
不要重复这个问题
was how do we deal with the data side of
就是我们如何处理
of microservices
微服务
yeah so the question is if there's a if
是的，所以问题是，如果有
there's one scheme or how do we deal in
有一个方案，或者我们如何应对
the microservices work um there's
微服务的工作
disclaimer we're not experts in the data
免责声明我们不是数据专家
side of things because we're framework
因为我们是框架
developers we actually have a PayPal
开发人员，我们实际上有一个PayPal
fellow here that might know a little bit
可能有点了解的人
more for his domain it depends on which
他的域名还有更多，取决于哪个
domain you're you're talking I know
域你在说我知道
about big moves to be able to adapt this
关于能够适应这一点的重大举措
there's a sure nothing Cole look like
肯定没有科尔的模样
like zone approach or you have one
像区域方法，或者您有一个
schema but it's actually Charlotte and
模式，但实际上是夏洛特和
then and then we have such an affinity
然后我们有如此的亲和力
going in and out so that the data is
进出，以便数据是
actually in one
实际上合而为一
oh so because we don't have distributed
哦，因为我们没有分配
transactions in paper we had never had
我们从未有过的纸质交易
it's always been service to service so
一直是服务到服务，所以
yeah a robot can be here a bit of a
是的，机器人可以在这里
challenge when something fails and then
挑战某事失败然后
you have to undo we follow more of an
您必须撤消，我们会遵循更多
architecture of the data is hidden
数据架构被隐藏
behind the service the JSON schema
服务背后的JSON模式
changes as new elements I'm not an
改变为我不是的新元素
expert on that to be honest but yeah you
说实话的专家，但是你
had a second question okay transaction
还有第二个问题可以交易
boundaries yeah the one thing I know is
是的，我知道的一件事是
PayPal is against distributed
贝宝反对分布式
transactions we don't do we tend not to
我们不做的交易我们往往不会
do distributed transactions I think this
我认为这是分布式交易
team must seem to be like because we
团队一定看起来像是因为我们
have this silo domains the database is
有这个筒仓域的数据库
actually fixed that the schemas are
实际解决方案是
fixed to the domain and then the
固定到域，然后
exchange of data happens to services he
数据交换发生在他的服务上
has it is with challenges especially
有挑战吗
when you talk about performance and SLA
当您谈论性能和SLA时
is because you gotta go to multiple
是因为你必须去多个
places to fetch data there's some ideas
取数据的地方有一些想法
around how we can fix some of that but
关于我们如何解决一些问题，
we're not the authority sources so yes
我们不是权威人士，所以是的
excellent question the question was how
很好的问题，问题是如何
do we deal with JDBC connections at the
我们如何处理JDBC连接
scale because we have a lot of a lot of
规模，因为我们有很多
instances and if each of them connects
实例，如果它们每个都连接
with the database we can bring it to
与数据库，我们可以将其带到
instances yes
实例是
paper is mostly Oracle RAC we have what
本文主要是Oracle RAC我们有什么
we call it I think we can call it JDBC
我们称它为JDBC
as a service yeah it's like a type for
作为一种服务，就像一种
JDBC driver yes yeah something like so
JDBC驱动程序是的，像这样
we have we have servers that are
我们有服务器
concentrators of connections those are
连接的集中器是
the guys that connect to the database
连接数据库的人
and have connection pooling and then we
并建立连接池，然后我们
have these driver to the application it
将这些驱动程序安装到应用程序中
presents itself as a JDBC driver but in
表现为JDBC驱动程序，但在
reality is using is not connected to the
现实正在使用未连接到
database its connecting to these
数据库连接到这些
services and it's multiplexing the
服务，并且多路复用
connection so is the service really that
连接真的是服务
has the connections and sessions for the
具有连接和会话
for the database and it's like a middle
对于数据库，就像一个中间人
layer it's like a level 4 I'm sorry can
就像第4级一样，抱歉
you repeat a bottleneck because we have
您重复瓶颈，因为我们有
to have the extra hobbies yeah yeah it's
拥有额外的爱好，是的，
been tuning this there's other probably
在调整这个可能还有其他
PayPal talks where you can say I think
贝宝在哪里可以说我认为
internal is called OCC yeah at some
内部在某些地方被称为OCC是的
point I think there was going to be some
我认为这将会有一些
work with Oracle to kind of promote it
与Oracle合作以促进它
into the industry how do you think that
进入行业，您如何看待
is basically a concentrator is yeah and
基本上是一个选矿厂
the whole idea was actually first of all
整个想法实际上首先
it's distributed as well it's not just
它不仅是分布式的
one single second we have we still have
一秒钟，我们还有，我们还有
many C++ applications right and there is
许多C ++应用程序正确存在
a lot of there's a lot of connection
很多很多的联系
pooling and caching and etc that is
池化和缓存等
already in place not just for Java
已经存在，而不仅仅是Java
applications but for C++ applications so
应用程序，但适用于C ++应用程序
this extra layer that we added takes
我们添加的这一额外层需要
care of all the different application
照顾所有不同的应用
types we're gonna talk a little bit more
我们将要谈论的类型
if you want of course we have time for
如果您当然想要，我们有时间
one more question
还有一个问题
Cupid or okapi the question was what is
丘比特或霍加api的问题是什么
our experience with Cupid since it's
我们对丘比特的经验，因为
been since it's going to be deprecated
因为它已经过时了
it's an experimental project the real
这是一个实验项目，真正的
goal is to use an AMQP one over call
目标是使用AMQP一通通话
Cupid was like the driver and they had
丘比特就像司机，他们有
that reactor actually Cupid reactor
那个反应堆实际上是丘比特反应堆
which looked interesting that's one the
看起来很有趣的是
payment space again we're not in that
支付空间再次我们不在那
division we just work with them and our
部门，我们只是与他们合作，
interaction with them was a lot with the
与他们的互动与
you don't want tomcat there because they
你不想在那儿举猫，因为他们
make sense so they were one of the main
有道理，所以他们是主要的人之一
drivers to validate that this work could
驱动程序来验证这项工作可以
be done if you want we can discuss
如果您愿意，可以完成讨论
afterwards and I can give you some names
之后，我可以给你一些名字
of people that you can contact them
您可以联系他们的人
talking alright thanks everybody for
说话很好，谢谢大家
being here I'm gonna hang out if you
在这里，如果你，我要出去玩
guys please one more question so more
大家请再问一个问题
questions for me thank you
给我的问题谢谢
you
您